refactor: optimize Desktop layout container
style: adjust aurora gradient positioning
feat: implement draggable TerminalWindow
fix: drag constraints on mobile
feat: add macOS traffic light buttons
style: update terminal background blur
refactor: extract TerminalContent component
feat: implement command history state
feat: add zustand terminal store
fix: auto-scroll behavior on new command
feat: implement TerminalInput with custom cursor
style: adjust blinking cursor animation
feat: add arrow key history navigation
refactor: modularize commandEngine parser
feat: implement whoami command
feat: implement about command
feat: implement skills command with progress bars
feat: implement projects command with grid layout
feat: implement experience timeline
feat: implement education command
feat: implement contact command
feat: add sudo hire harsh easter egg
feat: add coffee ascii art command
feat: add developer joke command
style: responsive design for mobile views
fix: ASCII banner wrapping on small screens
feat: implement neofetch system info
refactor: extract neofetch ASCII logo
style: update neofetch color scheme
feat: add CommandPalette component
feat: implement Cmd+K shortcut listener
style: glassmorphic spotlight search UI
feat: link palette actions to terminal commands
refactor: cleanup unused legacy components
fix: Next.js 15 Turbopack script tag error
refactor: remove next-themes dependency
style: enforce strict dark mode palette
feat: implement TerminalBoot sequence
style: randomize boot sequence delays
fix: hydration mismatch on boot timestamps
feat: persist boot timestamps in state
fix: terminal vertical centering on initial load
refactor: replace framer motion sizing with tailwind classes
feat: implement resume pdf viewer command
feat: copy resume pdf to public directory
feat: implement history print command
feat: implement theme toggle command
style: adjust input line flex wrapping
